bmw.ca 2017-05-14

# Privacy Policy

_How long is my personal information retained?_  
BMW Group Canada will retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws.

_How do you protect my personal information?_  
At BMW Group Canada we are committed to protecting the personal information in our possession. We use administrative and technical controls, and require our service providers to take such measures, to help to maintain the security of your personal information. We have implemented security measures which include the use of: physical secure data centres and premises; internal security policies and procedures; defined internal segregation of duties; and electronic access controls such as passwords and encryption technology. However, please note that no system of protection can guarantee the protection of your personal information.

In addition, we encourage you to observe safe computing practices. It is your responsibility to keep confidential the user-ID and password that you use to register with us and not share them with anyone. If you believe that your user-ID and password have been compromised, you can change them by editing your profile at our website www.bmw.ca or by contacting BMW Group Canada at the contact information in “ **Who do I contact if I have questions or concerns about privacy at BMW?** ” below.

In certain parts of this website where we require that you provide us with sensitive personal information such as credit card information, we will protect the security of your personal information during transmission by using industry standard encryption technology. Please only submit this sensitive information within the secure area of the website where it may be specifically requested. Please do not send sensitive personal information via non-secure areas, including by email.

_Where do you store my personal information?_  
We may use service providers who process or store information outside of Canada. In accordance with the laws of those countries, in certain circumstances your personal information may be accessible by foreign law enforcement, regulatory bodies or other authorities.

BMW Group Canada stores personal information in electronic format on servers located in the United States of America and maintained by various BMW entities in the United States.. These BMW entities may be compelled to disclose this information to governmental agencies or security forces in the United States of America if required to do so by U.S. law.

_How can I access my personal information?_  
At your request, we will let you know what personal information we have in our possession about you, what it is being used for, and to whom it has been disclosed. If you require access to your personal information please first check any account profiles that you have with us, such as your My BMW profile.

If you are unable to locate the personal information you require access to, please contact us at the contact information in “ **Who do I contact if I have questions or concerns about privacy at BMW?** ” below to request access. We will respond to your request within the time period prescribed by law. You may be requested to provide satisfactory identification and proof of entitlement to access your personal information. We will provide you with access to your personal information that is in our possession, subject to certain exceptions. For example, we may not provide you with your personal information where the information is subject to solicitor-client privilege or consists of references to other persons or proprietary information that cannot be severed from the record. There may be reasonable costs associated with your request.

_How can I correct and update my personal information?_  
We strive to keep the personal information in our possession or control accurate, complete, current and relevant, based on the most recent information available to us. If you would like to correct the accuracy of any personal information we have about you, you may modify your information using tools available to you (such as by editing your profile in your My BMW account) or by contacting us at the contact information in “Who do I contact if I have questions or concerns about privacy at BMW?” below.

If you have provided information about yourself in order to receive emails or product mailings and would like to modify your information, please contact one of our Customer Service Representatives by calling 1-800-567-2691 or by mail to Customer Service, BMW Group Canada, 50 Ultimate Drive, Richmond Hill, ON L4S 0C8.

_How do BMW retailers manage my personal information?_  
BMW retailers operate as separate and distinct legal entities from BMW Group Canada. Each retailer has its own privacy practices and policies and we are not responsible for their privacy practices or compliance with applicable privacy law. When communicating with a BMW retailer, we encourage you to review their privacy policy and practices to understand how they collect, use and disclose your personal information.

_How do third party applications collect my personal information?_  
Our websites may use third party social network plugins (“plug-ins”) from certain social networks.

When you visit a webpage that contains a plug-in, your browser establishes a direct connection with the servers of that third party social network. The content of the plug-in comes directly from the third party social network to your browser, which then integrates into our website. The plug-in provides the third party social network with the information that you have accessed the corresponding webpage of our website along with certain information, such as the date and time of access, and other browser-related information. If you are logged into the social network, the social network may also receive your user ID information and associate your activity with your account. If you interact with the plug-in, the corresponding information about your interaction or activity is transmitted from your browser directly to the third party social network and stored by it.

We do not control or collect the information collected by the plug-ins on our websites. Please carefully review the privacy practices of the third party social networks that provide the plug-ins to learn more about how they manage your personal information.

_Who do I contact if I have questions or concerns about privacy at BMW?_  
BMW Group Canada has developed policies and procedures to respond to individual complaints and questions relating to privacy. We will investigate and attempt to resolve all complaints. We will respond to your inquiry within the time period prescribed by law. Please be advised that there may be a reasonable cost associated with your request.

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact our Privacy Officer by email at privacy@bmw.ca; by telephone at 1-866-805-5853; or by mail at 50 Ultimate Drive, Richmond Hill, ON L4S 0C8.

We welcome your comments and emails but please note that any information, including but not limited to suggestions, ideas or submissions you make through and onto any BMW Group website will become the exclusive property of BMW Group Canada.
